Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume VII, issued 1910
  - 43. Division of Chemistry, 1910-1911, October 1, 1910 (HU 75.25 Box 19)
  - 44. Department of Landscape Architecture, 1910-1911, October 8, 1910 (HU 75.25 Box 18)
  - 45. Harvard Medical School, 1910-1911, December 15, 1910 (HU 75.25 Box 18)
- Volume VIII, issued 1911
  - 1. Harvard University catalogue, 1910-1911, January 2, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 19)
  - 2. Announcement of Harvard College, 1910-1911, January 10, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 3. Summer School of Medicine, announcement of courses, 1911, February 4, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 4. Brief announcement, Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1911, February 9, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 6. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1909-1910, March 1, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 17)
  - 7. Provisional announcement of courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1911-1912, March 15, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 8. Announcement of courses for graduates in the Harvard Medical School, 1911-1912, April 3, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 9. Students' expenses and college aids in Harvard College and in the Graduate Schools of Arts and Sciences, Applied Science, and Business Administration, April 10, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - Supplement to no. 9, S tudents' expenses and college aids, geographical list of scholarships, April 10, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 10. Graduate School of Applied Science, Bussey Institution, economic entomology, genetics, and comparative pathology, 1911-1912, April 15, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 11. Supplement, Music, April 20, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
    Scope and content
    Also contains Supplement 11, changes in courses in education, May 31, 1911.
  - 12. The Graduate School of Business Administration, 1911-1912, April 25, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 13. Graduate School of Applied Science, Division of Forestry, 1911-1912, April 29, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 14. Division of Engineering, Courses of instruction at the Engineering Camp at Squam Lake, New Hampshire, summer of 1911, May 2, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 15. Division of Medical Sciences, courses leading to the degrees of master of arts and doctor of philosophy, May 8, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 16. The Divinity School, announcement, 1911-1912, May 15, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 17. The Law School, announcements, 1911-1912, May 20, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 18. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1911-1912, May 25, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 19. Division of Physics, 1911-1912, May 29, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 20. Department of Architecture, 1911-1912, June 1, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 21. Division of the Fine Arts, 1911-1912, June 6, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 22. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1911-1912, June 10, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 23, extra edition. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1911-1912, second edition, September 25, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 24. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1911-1912, June 20, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 25. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1911-1912, second edition, June 24, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 25, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, third edition, September 20, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 26. History and technique of the drama, Department of English, departmental and allied courses in the drama, the MacDowell Resident Fellowship, the Craig Prize, 1911-1912, July 3, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 27. Division of Philosophy, 1911-1912, July 8, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 28. Division of Mathematics with the courses in astronomy, 1911-1912, July 14, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 29. Graduate School of Applied Science, civil, mechanical and electrical engineering, 1911-1912, July 18, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 30. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1911-1912, July 24, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 31. Rules relating to college studies, 1911-1912, July 29, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 32. Department of English, 1911-1912, August 2, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 32, extra edition. Department of English, 1911-1912, second edition, August 2, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 33. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1911-1912, August 9, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 34. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Dental School, June 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 35. Division of Chemistry, 1911-1912, August 19, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 20)
  - 36. Rank list, 1910-1911, August 25, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 37. Opportunities for religious worship, instruction, and fellowship, 1911-1912, August 30, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 38. Department of Zoology, 1911-1912, September 5, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 39. Division of Anthropology, 1911-1912, September 12, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 40. Department of Comparative Literature, 1911-1912, September 16, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 41. Division of Education, 1911-1912, September 21, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 42. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1911-1912, September 25, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 43. Department of Landscape Architecture, 1911-1912, September 27, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 44. Division of Music, 1911-1912, October 2, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 46. The Harvard Medical School, 1911-1912, with an announcement for 1912-1913,October 16, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 47. The Dental School, 1911-1912, with an announcement for 1912-1913, December 28, 1911 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
- Volume IX, issued 1912
  - 1. Harvard University catalogue, 1911-1912, January 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - 3. Summer School of Medicine, announcement of courses, 1912, February 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 4. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1912, February 8, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 6. Courses in pediatrics, 1912, March 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 7. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1912-1913, March 5, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 7, extra edition. Announcement of courses offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1912-1913, June 10, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 8. Reports of the President and Treasurer of Harvard College, 1910-1911, April 2, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 9, supplement. Education, April 10, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
    Includes No. 9, second announcement, Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1912, April 10, 1912.
  - 9, supplement. Psychology, April 10, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 10. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Engineering, 1912-1913, April 15, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - Supplement, no. 10, Division of Engineering Sciences, 1912-1913, April 15, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - Supplement, no. 10, Graduate Schools of Applied Science, courses in sanitary engineering, April 15, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 11. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Forestry, 1912-1913, April 20, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 12. Announcement of courses for graduates in the Harvard Medical School, 1912-1913, April 23, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 13. The Law School, 1912-1913, April 30, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 14. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1912-1913, May 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 14, extra edition. Graduate School of Business, 1912-1913, second edition, July 15, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 15. School of Engineering, the Engineering Camp at Squam Lake, New Hampshire, 1912, May 4, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 16. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1912-1913,May 10, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 16, extra edition. Division of History, Govenment and Economics, 1912-1913, second edition, September 20, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 17. Division of Anthropology, 1912-1913, May 14, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 18. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1912-1913, May 20, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 19. The Divinity School, 1912-1913, May 25, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 20. Graduate School of Applied Science, School of Landscape Architecture, 1912-1913, June 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 21. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1912-1913, June 8, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 22. Division of Philosophy, 1912-1913, June 15, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 23. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Architecture, 1912-1913, June 18, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 24. Division of Mathematics, with the courses in astronomy, June 19, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 25. Division of the Fine Arts, 1912-1913, June 22, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 26. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1912-1913, July 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 27. Division of Physics, 1912-1913, July 3, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 28. Department of Zoology, 1912-1913, July 10, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 30. Department of Comparative Literature, 1912-1913, July 20, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 31. History and technique of the drama, Department of English, departmental and allied courses in the drama, the MacDowell Resident Fellowship, the Craig Prize, 1912-1913, July 25, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 32. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, Bussey Institution, School of Applied Biology, 1912-1913, August 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 33. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Dental School, 1912, August 3, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 34. Department of English, 1912-1913, August 9, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 35. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Mining, 1912-1913, August 16, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 37. Rank list, 1912-1913 [1911-1912], August 30, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
    Misprinted date on cover.
  - 38. Department of Botany, 1912-1913, September 3, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 39. Division of Education, 1912-1913, September 5, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 40. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1912-1913, September 9, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 41. Rules relating to College studies, 1912-1913, September 11, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 42. Division of Chemistry, 1912-1913, September 18, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - 42, extra edition. Division of Chemistry, 1912-1913, second edition, October 19, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 43. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1912-1913, September 21, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 44. Division of Music, 1912-1913, October 1, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
  - 45. The Harvard Medical School, 1912-1913, with an announcement for 1913-1914, October 30, 1912 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
- Volume X, issued 1913
  - No. 1
    - No. 1, Part 1. Harvard University Catalogue, 1912-1913, January 1, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
    - No. 1, Part 2. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1913-1914, February 24, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
    - No. 1, Part 4. Student's expenses and college aids in Harvard College and in the Graduate Schools of Arts and Sciences, Applied Science, and Business Administration, April 14, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 5. Division of Engineering Sciences, 1913-1914, April 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 8. The Divinity School, 1913-1914, April 28, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 9. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1913-1914, May 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 9, extra edition. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1913-1914, second edition, July 9, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 10. Division of History, Government and Economics, 1913-1914, May 19, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 11. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1913-1914, May 20, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 12. Division of Mathematics, 1913-1914,May 29, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 13. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1913-1914, May 27, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 13, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1913-1914, January 12, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 13, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1913-1914, second edition, September 20, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 17. Division of Physics, with the courses in astronomy, 1913-1914, June 14, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 18. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1913-1914, June 17, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 19. Division of Education, 1913-1914, June 30, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 24. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Dental School, 1913, July 25, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 25. Division of Music, 1913-1914, July 28, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 26. Rules relating to College studies, 1913-1914, August 4, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 27. Division of Chemistry, 1913-1914, August 8, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 28. Department of English, 1913-1914, August 16, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 1, Part 30. The Graduate School of Arts, 1913-1914, September 4, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
  - No. 2
    - No. 2, Part 1. Reports of President and Treasurer, 1911-1912, February 20, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 21)
  - No. 3
    - No. 3, Part 1. Sanitary engineering at Harvard, 1913-1914, January 30, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 2. Summer courses in municipal sanitation, 1913, February 11, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 3. School of Engineering, the Engineering Camp at Squam Lake, New Hampshire, summer of 1913, March 10, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 4. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Engineering, summer session, 1913,March 18, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 5. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Engineering, 1913-1914, April 21, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 6. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, School of Forestry, 1913-1914, April 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 8. Graduate Schools of Applied Science, Mining School, 1913-1914, July 15, 1813 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 9. Graduate School of Applied Science, Landscape Architecture, August 5, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 3, Part 29. Rank list for 1912-1913, August 20, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 22)
  - No. 4
    - No. 4, Part I. Graduate School of Medicine at the Harvard Medical School, catalogue for the summer term, 1913, May 21, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 4, Part 2. Graduate School of Medicine, annual catalogue, 1913-1914, first edition, announcement of courses, October 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 24)
    - No. 4, Part 3. The Harvard Medical School, 1913-1914, with an announcement for 1914-1915, October 20, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
  - No. 5
    - No. 5, Part 1. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1913, February 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 5, Part I. Supplements on botany and education, February 15, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 5, Part 2. Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1913, excursions to places of historical and literary interest in Eastern Massachusetts, February 27, 1913 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
- Volume XI, issued 1914
  - No. 1
    - No. 1, Part 1. Harvard University catalogue, 1913-1914, January 1, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 1, Part 2. Announcement of Harvard College, 1913-1914, January 8, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 1, Part 3. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1914-1915, February 25, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 4. Division of Education, 1914-1915, February 26, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 7. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1914-1915, April 17, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 7, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1914-1915, second edition,September 21, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 8. Reports of President and Treasurer of Harvard College, 1912-1913, April 20, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 23)
    - No. 1, Part 9. The Divinity School, 1914-1915, April 22, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - Supplement, No. 1, Part 9. Divinity School faculty letter, April 22, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 10. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1914-1915, preliminary announcement, April 27, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 11. Department of Engineering Sciences, 1914-1915, May 4, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 27)
    - No. 1, Part 14. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1914-1915, May 19, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 15. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1914-1915, May 22, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 16. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1914-1915, May 25, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 22. Division of Chemistry, 1914-1915, June 18, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 26. Department of English, 1914-1915, July 14, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 27. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Dental School, June 1914, July 25, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 28. Rank list for 1913-1914, August 4, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 1, Part 29. Rules relating to College studies, 1914-1915, August 7, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 30. Graduate School of Business Administration, final edition, 1914-1914, August 10, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 1, Part 31. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1914-1915, September 18, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
  - No. 2
    - No. 2, Part I. Publications of the Harvard University Press,May 6, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
  - No. III
    - No. 3, Part I. The Engineering Camp at Squam Lake, New Hampshire, summer of 1914, March 28, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 27)
    - No. 3, Part 4. Announcement of courses in the School of Engineering for the summer of 1914 and the academic year, 1914-1915, April 25, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 3, Part 6. Announcement of courses in the Mining School, 1914-1915, June 1, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 3, Part 7. Graduate School of Architecture and Landscape Architecture, School of Landscape Architecture, 1914-1915, August 5, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
  - No. IV
    - No. 4, Part I. Graduate School of Medicine at the Harvard Medical School, catalogue for the summer term, 1914, May 18, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 4, Part 2. Graduate School of Medicine, announcement of the School of Tropical Medicine, 1914-1915, August 5, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 4, Part 3. Graduate School of Medicine, annual catalogue, 1914-1915, first edition, September 10, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 4, Part 3, extra edition. Graduate School of Medicine, annual catalogue, 1914-1915, second edition, December 30, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 4, Part 4. The Harvard Medical School, 1914-1915, with an announcement for 1915-1916, December 28, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 4, Part 5. The Dental School, 1914-1915, with an announcement for 1915-1916, December 30, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
  - No. V
    - Supplement, No. 5, Part I. Summer session, July 1-August 12, 1914. English: Oral English and Public Speaking, February 21, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
    - No. 5, Part 3. Summer School of Arts and Sciences, excursions to places of historical and literary interest in eastern Massachusetts, April 3, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 27)
    - No. 5, Part 4. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1914, May 27, 1914 (HU 75.25 Box 26)
- Volume XII, issued 1915
  Incomplete. Lacks Vol. XII, No. 1, Part 1. Harvard University Catalogue, 1914-1915, January 1, 1915.
  - No. 1
    - No. 1, Part 3. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1915-1916, February 10, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 4. Information for students who intend to enter the freshman class in Harvard College in 1915, description of the freshman halls, February 18, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 5. Division of Education, 1915-1916, February 25, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 6. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1915-1916, preliminary edition, February 27, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - Supplement No. I, Part 6. Teaching the profession of business at Harvard, February 27, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 6, extra edition. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1915-1916, final edition, September 17, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 7. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1913-1914, March 1, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 25)
    - No. 1, Part 8. Students' expense and College aids in Harvard College and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, March 8, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 11. The Divinity School, 1915-1916, March 30, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - Supplement, No. 1, Part II. Divinity School of Harvard University, March 30, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 12. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Engineering Sciences, 1915-1916, April 6, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 13. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1915-1916, first edition, April 12, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 13, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1915-1916, second edition, September 20, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 14. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Social Ethics, 1915-1916, April 28, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 14, extra edition. Division of History, Government, Economics, 1915-1916, second edition, September 25, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 15. Division of Mathematics, 1915-1916, May 10, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 16. Department of French and other Romance languages and literatures, 1915-1916, May 14, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 17. Division of the Fine Arts, 1915-1916, May 25, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 18. Division of Chemistry, 1915-1916, May 28, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 20. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1915-1916, June 8, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 21. Division of Anthropology, 1915-1916, June 10, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 22. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1915-1916, June 12, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 23. Department of Zoology, 1915-1916, June 15, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 24. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics, with the courses in astronomy, 1915-1916, June 25, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 28)
    - No. 1, Part 25. Religious life at Harvard, by Edward Caldwell Moore, July 6, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 26. Department of English, 1915-1916, July 10, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 27. Department of Botany, 1915-1916, July 26, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 28, No. 1. Rank list for 1914-1915, July 28, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 27)
    - No. 1, Part 29. Rules relating to College studies, 1915-1916, August 2, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 31. Department of Comparative Literature, 1915-1916, August 10, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 32. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1915-1916, September 1, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)
    - No. 1, Part 33. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1915-1916, September 8, 1915 (HU 75.25 Box 29)